(Sheldon:)...have you ever wondered
why my little toes and lateral incisors...
(Sheldon:)...are significantly smaller
than the average for someone of my size?
(Leonard:)I wonder a lot of things about you,
Sheldon, but not that.
(Sheldon:)Well, those are indicators...
(Sheldon:)...that I'm farther along the evolutionary
scale than the average human.
- No kidding?
- Yeah, wait, no, I'm not gonna so far...
(Sheldon:)...as to say that I represent
a distinct new stage in humankind.
(Sheldon:)You know, a Homo novus, if you will.
(Sheldon:)No, that's for anthropologists to decide.
(Sheldon:)But I am convinced
that the reason I cannot master...
(Sheldon:)...the plebeian task of driving
is because I'm not meant to.
(Leonard:)Yes, you are.
You're meant to learn how to drive.
(Leonard:)- Please learn how to drive.
- No, no.
(Sheldon:)I'm meant for greater things, like
unraveling the mysteries of the universe...
(Sheldon:)...not determining when it's safe to pass
a stopped school bus on a country road.
- It's never safe.
- Yeah, well, I know that now.